ILGWU Western States Region Records 5780/115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Gallant of California, Incorporated, 1962-1963 (Box 81, Folder 53)
- Harry Garber, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 54)
- Philippe Garnet, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 55)
- Garey Brothers, Incorporated, 1963-1965 (Box 81, Folder 56)
- Ingenue of California, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 57)
- General Sweater, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 58)
- Helene Gary: Contractor, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 59)
- J&E Sportswear, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 60)
- J&B Manufacturing Company, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 61)
- Jan-Bra, Incorporated, 1959-1968 (Box 81, Folder 62)
- J&M of California, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 63)
- Jabberwocky, 1967-1969 (Box 81, Folder 64)
- Jackie of Hollywood, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 65)
- Jackney Sportswear Company, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 66)
- Jan Originals, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 67)
- Jan Sue, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 68)
- Jane Cristy and Company (Box 81, Folder 69)
- Kay, Janice, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 70)
- Jax of California, 1954-1969 (Box 81, Folder 71)
- Jay Brothers of California, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 72)
- Jean of California, 1963-1966 (Box 81, Folder 73)
- Jean-Louis and Company, 1962-1963 (Box 81, Folder 74)
- Jenny Ann, 1963-1966 (Box 81, Folder 75)
- Julie Miller of California, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 76)
- Jeri Bee of California, 1962-1964 (Box 81, Folder 77)
- Jet Set of California, 1964-1969 (Box 81, Folder 78)
- Jet Sportswear Company, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 79)
- Jody Sportswear, 1961-1967 (Box 81, Folder 80)
- De Johnson, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 81)
- Judy Ann of California, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 82)
- Judy's Fashion, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 83)
- K.C. Products, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 84)
- Kader, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 85)
- Irving Kahn, Incorporated, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 86)
- Karinda of California, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 87)
- Kathy of California, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 88)
- Mamie Kay (Box 81, Folder 89)
- Kay Modes (Box 81, Folder 90)
- Kiku's Sewing Company, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 91)
- Kitty of Los Angeles, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 92)
- Kiyyo Kasuals, 1964-1967 (Box 81, Folder 93)
- Koppie Kat, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 94)
- Hal Krasell of California, Incorporated, 1966-1967 (Box 81, Folder 95)
- Kosala, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 96)
- Frank Kraus, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 97)
- L&M (Box 81, Folder 98)
- Kwik Kutting Service, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 99)
- Leland Sportswear (Box 81, Folder 100)
- Lebanon of California, 1956-1967 (Box 81, Folder 101)
- Eve Le Coq., 1966 (Box 81, Folder 102)
- Lee Mar, 1959-1961 (Box 81, Folder 103)
- Lidia Originals, 1966-1967 (Box 81, Folder 104)
- Lillian of California, 1969 (Box 81, Folder 105)
- Lillie Sportswear, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 106)
- Alexander Lipton, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 107)
- Lisa Bella, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 108)
- Lisa Originals, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 109)
- Look West, Incorporated, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 110)
- Lordleigh of California, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 111)
- Lorian Juniors (Box 81, Folder 112)
- Lottie, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 113)
- Peggy Lou (Box 81, Folder 114)
- ILGWU: Regional Councils, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles Joint Board: Agreements, 1974 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Independent Agreements, 1973-1977 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Designers Guild: Local 452, 1973-1974 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Agreements, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association: Bulletin, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- ILGWU: Auditing Department, 1972-1973 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Agreements, 1971-1977 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Agreements, 1973-1977 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Proposals and Agreements, 1959-1973 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Tanne Negotiations, 1975-1977 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Contract Agreements, 1970-1974 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO, 1976 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous: Agreements, Statements and Lists, 1974-1976 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- District Councils: Merger Forms, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Wolfe, Max: Files Received, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Bernie Cowan, Incorporated, 1974-1976 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Emblem Manufacturing Company: Negotiations, 1973-1975 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Company III, Incorporated, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- SK&K Manufacturing Company, 1974-1975 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Messerman Sportswear, 1973-1975 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Local 97: Executive Board, 1973-1975 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Joint Board Funds, 1971-1975 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Warehouse Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Local 55: Executive Board, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Local 97 Business and Local Meetings, 1963-1971 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- New Members, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Agenda for Western States Region Appeals Committee Meeting, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Retirement: Severance Health, 1970-1977 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- ILGWU: Employers Vacation Health and Welfare Fund, 1973-1975 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Managers Report, 1973-1975 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- ILGWU: Vacation, Health, Death and Welfare, 1965-1969 (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Staff: Dues, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Monthly: Shop Chairman Inter-Union Office Guidance Information [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1977 (Box 83, Folder 20)
- Monthly: Shop Chairman Inter-Union Office Guidance Information [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1977 (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Shop Reports (Box 83, Folder 22)
- LouBella: House Calls, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Cloak Shops: Los Angeles (Box 84, Folder 2)
- New Election: LouBella, 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Los Angeles: Sportswear, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles: Draperies, Spreads, Aprons, Curtains (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles: Junior, Teens, Childrens and Infants wear (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles: Dresses (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles: Accessories (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles: Blouse, Skirts, Slacks and Shirts (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Frank Lee: House Call Sheets, 1964-1972 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Open Shops, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- LouBella Elections, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Jones Leisure Products, Limited, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Meisel Fabrics, Incorporated, 1969-1970 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Mister Marty, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- M.W. Manufacturing Company, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Maurice Slacks, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Novis Denne of Arizona, Incorporated, 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Organization Department Finance: San Francisco, 1965-1972 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- ILGWU Los Angeles Joint Board: Office Staff, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Smith, Ralph: Open shop Reports, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Permission Forms: Union Members in Open Shops, 1971-1972 (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Pillows of California: House Calls, 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 23)
- Pillows of California, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 84, Folder 24)
- Murray Rosen Company, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 25)
- Sir James, Incorporated: Local 84, 1970-1972 (Box 84, Folder 26)
- Surf and Turf, 1970-1972 (Box 84, Folder 27)
- Smith, Ralph: Copie of Leaflets, 1971-1972 (Box 84, Folder 28)
- Severance Pay and Other Benefits, 1969-1972 (Box 84, Folder 29)
- Starlight Trading, 1971 (Box 84, Folder 30)
- California Schiffli, 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 31)
- California Schiffli, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 32)
- Sir James, Incorporated: Agreement, 1972-1973 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Terry Tuck Employees Group, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Tom Boy of California (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Union, Non-Union: Rothschild, Fredericks, Anjac Fashions, 1971-1973 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Aldik Artificial Flowers, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Arizona File, 1960-1970 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Vote No: Los Angeles, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Chic Linerie Leaflets, 1970-1971 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Attendance Sheets Chic Lingerie, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Collegian Sportswear, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Cory Marker Corporation, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Dale Sportswear, 1969-1970 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- General Leaflets Distribution, 1970-1973 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Sirje of California, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- California Infanteen Togs, Incorporated, 1962-1972 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- California Infanteen Togs, Incorporated, 1964-1965 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- J.C. Incorporated, J.S.E., 1972 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- Lou Gene of California, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- Frank Lee Production, 1972-1973 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- Sport Time, 1968-1972 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Salzberg, Samuel, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- Staff Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 85, Folder 22)
- Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 85, Folder 23)
- Joni Blair, Incorporated, 1972-1973 (Box 85, Folder 24)
- Associated Lace, Company, Incorporated, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 25)
- Daisy of California, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 26)
- Lebanon of California, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 27)
- Alpaq and Alfred Paquete, Incorporated, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 28)
- Daisy of California, Incorporated, 1967-1968 (Box 85, Folder 29)
- Chic Lingerie Company, Incorporated, 1971 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Chic Lingerie Company, Incorporated: Current [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Chic Lingerie Company, Incorporated: Current [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Emblem Manufacturing Company, 1973-1974 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Excellent Fashions of California, 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Galanos (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Geno of California, Ricco of California, G.O. of California, 1965-1966 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Grenell Manufacturing Company, 1970-1971 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Grenell Sportswear, 1970-1971 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Committee Authorization: Miss Pat, 1966-1972 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Miss Pat: Leaflets, 1970-1971 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Miss Pat: Legal Information [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1972 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Miss Pat: Legal Information [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1972 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Committee Authorization: Mode-O-Sports, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- House Calls Completed: Texfi West, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Chips of California, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Catalina-Plus, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Mary Ann Rosenfeld, Incorporated (Box 87, Folder 4)
- J.J. and Company, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Koret of California (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Warehouses (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Gen-Way of California, 1976-1977 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Duro-Press: Branch of Paragon West (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Personal File, 1970-1973 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Pena, Victoria, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Martinez, Blanca, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Alday, Fernando, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Cristerna, Rosalia, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Hernandez, Silvino Cruz, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Velez, Irene, 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Castryon, Margarita, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Chavez, Teodoro, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 18)
- Cali, Mercedes, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 19)
- Camarena, Jose, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 20)
- Cano, Javier, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 21)
- Castro, Lila De, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 22)
- Diaz, Pedro, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 23)
- Drizo, Fortunato, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 24)
- Zamora, Juana, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 25)
- Diaz, Esther, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 26)
- Dominguez, Wilerido, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 27)
- Matias, Fermin Alfonso, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 28)
- Moron, Irene, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 29)
- Marquez, Paulino, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 30)
- Marroquin, Martha, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 31)
- Martinez, Rigoberto, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 32)
- Nunez, Manuela I., 1975 (Box 87, Folder 33)
- Nunez, Maria Carmen, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 34)
- Inunez, Manuela, 1975-1976 (Box 87, Folder 35)
- Olivares, Benjamin, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 36)
- Olivares, Angel, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 37)
- Diaz, Tomasa Palacios, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 38)
- Perez, Angela, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 39)
- Rivas, Francisca, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 40)
- Lazaro, Paula Rios, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 41)
- Sanchez, Maria Fidela, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 42)
- Soto, Consuelo, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 43)
- Torres, Lina, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 44)
- Zapien, Francisca, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 45)
- Gardea, Josefina, 1972-1975 (Box 87, Folder 46)
- Garcia, Adelina, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 47)
- Garcia, Carlos, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 48)
- Gardea, Maria, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 49)
- Gomez, Hilario, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 50)
- Lopez, Maria G., 1973-1975 (Box 87, Folder 51)
- Ramos, Maria C., 1975 (Box 87, Folder 52)
- Morales, Adelina Ortega, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 53)
- Smith, Ralph: Legal Papers Arpeja-California, Incorporated, 1970-1973 (Box 87, Folder 54)
- Chic Lingerie Company, Incorporated: Votes, 1970-1972 (Box 87, Folder 55)
- Chic Lingerie Company, Incorporated Legal Letters: Smith, Ralph, 1970-1971 (Box 87, Folder 56)
- Mr. Charles, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 57)
- D.B. Sportswear, 1963-1965 (Box 87, Folder 58)
- Daches Embroidery Company, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 59)
- D'Alessandro, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 60)
- Valorie Dale (Box 87, Folder 61)
- Dana Lana of California, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 62)
- D'Anna Garment, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 63)
- W.R. Darling and Son, 1966-1969 (Box 87, Folder 64)
- Deena Lingerie, 1969 (Box 87, Folder 65)
- Della Rossa Boutique, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 66)
- Deni Casuals, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 67)
- De Michel Originals (Box 87, Folder 68)
- Desert Palm Shirt Company, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 69)
- Deewse Swimwear, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 70)
- Di Bias of California (Box 87, Folder 71)
- Dixie Bias, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 72)
- Dolly Kader, Incorporated (Box 87, Folder 73)
- Dominique, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 74)
- Tom D'Amico, 1963-1968 (Box 87, Folder 75)
- Michael Domroy, 1962-1966 (Box 87, Folder 76)
- Dor-Cal of California, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 77)
- Dorsey Company, 1962-1966 (Box 87, Folder 78)
- Lilly Diamond, 1963-1964 (Box 87, Folder 79)
- Duet Knitting, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 80)
- Duroy Manufacturing Company, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 81)
- Duchess of California, 1966-1969 (Box 87, Folder 82)
- Dove Manufacturing Company [folder 1 of 2], 1958-1967 (Box 87, Folder 83)
- Dove Manufacturing Company [folder 2 of 2], 1958-1967 (Box 87, Folder 84)
- Dove Manufacturing Company [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1966 (Box 87, Folder 85)
- Dove Manufacturing Company [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1966 (Box 87, Folder 86)
- Chic Lingerie, 1970 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Joe Accordino, Incorporated, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Central States Region: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Local 277, 1971-1973 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Local 278, 1971-1973 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Local 289, 1971-1973 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Local 294, 1968-1973 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Local 385, 1971-1973 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Local 430, 1971-1973 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Chic Lingerie: License Numbers, 1970-1971 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Chic Lingerie [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1972 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Chic Lingerie [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1972 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Chic Lingerie: Strike Benefits, 1970-1971 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- California Labor Federation: Convention Credentials, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Atlantic Richfield Company: Credit Cards, 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 15)
- Mobil Credit Cards, 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 16)
- Federal Mediation Services, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board: Reports [ folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board: Reports [ folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 19)
- ILGWU Benefits: Financial Statements, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 20)
- Arizona-Utah District Council, 1970-1973 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Travel Invoices, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Germaine Bouffard, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Gold Brothers, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous, 1968-1971 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Record of Long Distance Calls, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Southern California District Council, 1971-1973 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Seattle, Washington: Local 184, 1969-1973 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Local 270, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Local 271, 1972-1973 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Local 293, 1972-1973 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Local 451, 1972-1973 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Local 497, 1972-1973 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Los Angeles Joint Board: Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Staff: Gasoline Expenses and Car Repair Receipts, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 15)
- Cal-Mart Travel Service, 1972-1974 (Box 89, Folder 16)
- California Health Plan: Dr. Charles Slocumb, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Belt Shops, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Ram Knitting Mills: House Calls, 1971-1972 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Independent Agreement: Accessories, Bias Bindings, 1971-1974 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Contacts, 1971-1972 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Smith, Ralph: Personal File, 1970-1974 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Shop Chairman Visitation Reports, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Contacts [folder 1 of 2], 1957-1974 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Contacts [folder 2 of 2], 1957-1974 (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Election and Objection Committee Final Reports, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Elections, 1971-1977 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Dun and Bradstreet Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Delinquent Employers and Quarterly Reports, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Elections, 1961-1974 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Blue Cross, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Belt Manufacturers: Agreements and Charges, 1971-1974 (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Bernstein, Ted, 1975-1976 (Box 90, Folder 18)
- American Labor ORT, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 19)
- Firms, 1971-1975 (Box 90, Folder 20)
- ILGWU Convention: Correspondence From San Francisco, 1973-1974 (Box 90, Folder 21)
- Impartial Chairman, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 22)
- Complaints: Newspaper Articles, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 23)
- Firms, 1971-1974 (Box 90, Folder 24)
- Patricia Belt Company, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 25)
- Contracts, 1967-1972 (Box 90, Folder 26)
- Belt Companies: Agreements and Contracts [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1974 (Box 90, Folder 27)
- Belt Companies: Agreements and Contracts [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1974 (Box 90, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 90, Folder 29)
- Supervisor's Report, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Los Angeles Apparel Accessories Association: Agreements, 1971-1973 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Regional Election Call, Election Procedures and Material [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Regional Election Call, Election Procedures and Material [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1974 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Employers Contributions, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Feinberg, Basil, 1972-1975 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Golden Club, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Histadrut, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 9)
- Department of Industrial Relations, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Employers Vacation Health and Welfare Fund: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 11)
- Industrial Welfare Department, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Financial Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Financial Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Employers Vacation, Health and Welfare Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Seventy-Fifth Anniversary Celebration, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Justice, 1973-1975 (Box 91, Folder 18)
- Label Distribution and Label Reports, 1972-1975 (Box 91, Folder 19)
- Leviton, Philip, 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 20)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Contractors Association, 1969-1975 (Box 91, Folder 21)
- Los Angeles Coat and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1973-1975 (Box 91, Folder 22)
- Levin, Douglas: Vice President, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 23)
- Los Angeles County Federation of Labor, ALF-CIO, 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 24)
- Meetings, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 25)
- Memorandums, 1973-1975 (Box 91, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 91, Folder 27)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1975-1976 (Box 91, Folder 28)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 29)
- Wall, Cornelius: Correspondence, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 30)
- Teper, Lazare: Director Research Department, 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 31)
- Tyler, Gus: Assistant President, 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 32)
- Union Label Department, 1974-1976 (Box 91, Folder 33)
- United Farm Workers, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 34)
- Wall, Cornelius: Letters of Members, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 35)
- Seattle, Portland: Chairladies Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1975 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Seattle, Portland: Chairladies Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1975 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Portland, 1969-1973 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- P.C.O. Data, 1970-1971 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Olympiad Sportswear, 1970-1975 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Nifty Costume Company, 1972-1975 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Miss Pat, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Southern California District Council, 1971-1975 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Convention, 1970-1971 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Credit Union, 1972-1975 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Brass, Louis: Finance Office, 1968-1970 (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Irene, Incorporated, 1968-1970 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Danica Sport Company, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 13)
- Donley Blouse Company, 1972-1974 (Box 92, Folder 14)
- Employers Wage Proposal, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous, 1969-1975 (Box 92, Folder 16)
- Bye, Arnold: Welfare Funds Control Department, 1967-1968 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Teamsters, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Board of Trustees: ILGWU Employers Vacation, Health and Welfare Fund, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Paramount Trends, Incorporated, 1975-1976 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Montgomery Wards, 1974-1976 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- French Company, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Paramount Trends, 1975-1976 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Jan-Dee-Lee, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Helga, Incorporated, 1973-1975 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- C&C Sportswear: White, Ken, 1972-1974 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- C&C Sportswear, 1970-1975 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Rio Sportswear, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- King Valley Sportswear, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Anything File, 1971-1974 (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Moran Drapery, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 15)
- Don Rancho, Incorporated: Organizing, 1973-1975 (Box 93, Folder 16)
- Nally's Uniforms, 1974-1975 (Box 93, Folder 17)
- Robac Manufacturing Company, 1974-1975 (Box 93, Folder 18)
- Kathi Din, Incorporated, 1974-1975 (Box 93, Folder 19)
- Action Age, 1974-1975 (Box 93, Folder 20)
- Political: California Labor For Humphrey, 1968-1974 (Box 93, Folder 21)
- Paramount Trends, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 22)
- American Labor ORT, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 23)
- Office Employees International Union Local 30: Office Workers Contracts, 1961-1969 (Box 93, Folder 24)
- Daisy of California, General Knit Corporation: Non-Union Shops, 1974-1975 (Box 93, Folder 25)
- Los Angeles-Orange Counties Organizing Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 93, Folder 26)
- Stulberg, Louis: Bulletins, 1966-1975 (Box 93, Folder 27)
- Stulberg, Louis: Correspondence and Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 93, Folder 28)
- Resignation Forms: Signed and Blank, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 29)
- Health Center: Los Angeles, 1951-1974 (Box 93, Folder 30)
- Board of Trustees of the ILGWU Employers Vacation Health and Welfare Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 93, Folder 31)
- Histadrut, 1973-1975 (Box 93, Folder 32)
- Los Angeles Dress and Sportswear Joint Board: Resignations, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 33)
- Impartial Chairman, 1968-1974 (Box 93, Folder 34)
- ILGWU Convention: Resolutions, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 35)
- Lipsig, James, 1968-1969 (Box 93, Folder 36)
- National Prepaid Health Plan, Incorporated, 1973-1974 (Box 93, Folder 37)
- ILGWU: Legal Department, 1968-1975 (Box 93, Folder 38)
- Label Distribution Department: Levitan, Philip Correspondence, 1959-1975 (Box 93, Folder 39)
- Labor Management Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 93, Folder 40)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1972-1975 (Box 93, Folder 41)
- Terri Lee Manufacturing Company, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 42)
- Local 184, 1973-1974 (Box 93, Folder 43)
- Local 70, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 44)
- Health and Retirement Programs: Miscellaneous Plants, 1960-1974 (Box 93, Folder 45)
- ILGWU: Health Services Plan, 1969-1973 (Box 93, Folder 46)
- Sir James, Incorporated, 1969-1975 (Box 93, Folder 47)
- Stephen Laurie of California, 1968-1969 (Box 93, Folder 48)
- Sea Darlings of California, Incorporated, 1973 (Box 93, Folder 49)
- Severance Forms (Box 93, Folder 50)
- D&M, 1974-1975 (Box 93, Folder 51)
- ILGWU: Death Benefit, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 52)
- Marical, Margarita [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1976 (Box 94, Folder 1)